{
    "subject": "resource/Hidayat_Orujov",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Hidayat Khudush oglu Orujov (Azerbaijani: Hiday\u0259t Orucov Xudu\u015f o\u011flu; born September 5, 1944) is a notable writer and an Azerbaijani politician serving as the Chairman of State Committee for Work with Religious Organizations of Azerbaijan Republic.During the Karabakh movement and days leading up to the Sumgait pogrom of Armenians, Orujov threatened the Armenian population of Sumgait to \"break into your houses, torch your apartments, rape your women, and kill your children\".",
    "human_readable": "Hidayat Orujov's abstract is a notable writer and an Azerbaijani politician serving as the Chairman of State Committee for Work with Religious Organizations of Azerbaijan Republic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9072134494781494,
            "question": "What is the title of Hidayat Orujov's role in the Azerbaijani government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8919061422348022,
            "question": "What organization is Hidayat Orujov the Chairman of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677178025245667,
            "question": "In which country does Hidayat Orujov serve as a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8650978207588196,
            "question": "What position does Hidayat Orujov hold in the Azerbaijani government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143676519393921,
            "question": "Is Hidayat Orujov primarily known for his political or writing career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.801276683807373,
            "question": "What type of work does Hidayat Orujov engage in as a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7960987687110901,
            "question": "What is Hidayat Orujov known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.716889500617981,
            "question": "What is the name of the organization that Hidayat Orujov leads?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6579551100730896,
            "question": "Besides being a writer, what other role does Hidayat Orujov fulfill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.62245112657547,
            "question": "What nationality is Hidayat Orujov?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hidayat Orujov's abstract is a notable writer and an Azerbaijani politician serving as the Chairman of State Committee for Work with Religious Organizations of Azerbaijan Republic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides being a writer, what other role does Hidayat Orujov fulfill?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the organization that Hidayat Orujov leads?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Hidayat Orujov known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5556_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!  I can help with that."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the provided documents supports the given statement about Hidayat Orujov being a notable writer and an Azerbaijani politician who serves as the Chairman of the State Committee for Work with Religious Organizations of Azerbaijan Republic."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}